CONTACT

PHONE: +30 6984 314 864 EMAIL: v.kokkinos@protonmail.ch

About me:

I am a 27 years old dedicated, self-inspired and friendly individual. I work well in a team but also on my own as I like to set goals which I will achieve. I have good listening and communication skills. I am very willing to learn and develop new skills. I have a creative mind and am always up for new challenges. I am well organized and always plan ahead to make sure I manage my time well.

INTERESTS

- Penetration testing.
- Software Development.
- Game Development.
- Web design.
- Automation.
- Learning new languages (Spanish, Japanese, Russian).
- Technologies Enthusiast.
- Sports and Extreme Sports (Basketball, Motocross).
- Photography & Videography.
- Music and Drawing.

EXTERNAL LINKS

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/vasilis-kokkinos-492b1b170/

GitHub:

Thesis Project (Dino-Fight) https://github.com/redbillis

CodePen:

https://codepen.io/redbillis

Vasilis kokkinos

EDUCATION

2012-today Technological Educational Institute of Crete, Electronic and Communications Engineering (Currently attending)

Aspra Spitia High School, Aspra Spitia (Viotia, Greece), GR Graduation Certificate, 2012

SKILLS

Microsoft Windows	GNU/Linux	Microsoft Office	
Electrical Engineering	Robotics	Game Development	
Web Development	Python	C++	
HTML5	CSS	JavaScript	

SOFT SKILLS

Teamwork	Logical skills	Creativity	Accountability
Self-Management	Adaptability	Customer Servic	e Patience

LANGUAGES

Greek(Native)

English (Certificate of Competency in English, University of Michigan)

EXPERIENCE

October 2020 – November 2020. Internship as an Electronic Engineer at Mytilineos S.A., Central Greece, Agios Nikolaos.

June 2021 – October 2021. Internship as Technical Support Engineer at EpirusNET O.E., Arta Epirus, Greece.

SIDE NOTES

I served in the mandatory Greek Army for nine months in Greece and Cyprus. I've worked for about ten years as a waiter (Customer Service and Managing skills).